tageverycar.com 2011-11-26

# OWOW : : ONE WORLD WEBSITE INC

**One World One Website Privacy Statement**

Thank you for visiting www.oneowrldonewebsite.com or the Personal Website of your authorized One World One Website Business Owner whose name appears on the site (our "Site"). This Site is powered by One World One Website, Inc. (OWOW) and made available by OWOW as a service to your Affiliates. As used in this Privacy Statement, the terms “our,” “we,” and “us” refer to both OWOW and our Affiliates unless the context clearly provides otherwise.

We appreciate the opportunity to interact with you on the internet and are committed to protecting and safeguarding your privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to inform you about the types of information we might collect about you when you visit our Site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, that information.

**What Information We Collect and How We Use It**

Any information we collect on our Site generally falls into the following two categories:

**1\. Personally Identifiable Information**

This refers to information that lets us know who you are or things specifically about you.

**Visitors**

You can browse our Site using the Visitor function without revealing any Personally Identifiable Information. If you want to register or place an order and do not have a sponsoring Affiliate, you may voluntarily provide Personally Identifiable Information (such as name, address, email address, a telephone number) to be shared with an authorized I Affiliate near you for the purpose of contacting you, including via email, to assist with registration and ordering. In such event, we might maintain a record of your contact, including such Personally Identifiable Information, in a file specific to you. We use this information to provide better service in the event that you contact us again. 

**  Registration **

When you register to become an Affiliate and start your own I-commerce business powered by OWOW, or when you register to shop online as a Customer, enjoying full access to the many products and services available on our Site, we will collect Personally Identifiable Information (such as name, address, email address, and telephone number). This Personally Identifiable Information is securely stored and may be accessed under Contact Information. You are assigned an identification number and select your own password – both are needed to enter the Site and to access your Contact Information. 

**Ordering**

When you place an order for products or services, we collect Personally Identifiable Information (such as name, contact and billing information, credit card, and other transaction information). We use this information to deliver your order, process payment, and to communicate with you about the status of your order. 

**Credit Card Storage**

Credit card information collected at registration or for shopping cart orders is used only to process payment for the transaction and, generally, is not retained on our Site. You may, however, voluntarily elect to securely store a personal credit card to be used for shopping cart orders, Auto Renew,  and Standing Order features. You may add, edit, and delete your stored card information. 

**Surveys and Promotions**

From time to time you may voluntarily provide Personally Identifiable Information to complete surveys and questionnaires or to participate in user polls. We use this information to improve our products and services. We may also use your Personally Identifiable Information to provide you newsletters and other marketing information that coincide with your preferences. You may customize your marketing preferences, or let us know if you do not wish to receive any promotional materials, by adjusting your Subscriptions & Email options on the Site. 

**2\. Aggregate Information**

This refers to information that does not, by itself, identify you as a specific individual. Such information would include the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the website that referred you to our Site, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address (a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the web), your operating system and browser type, and any search terms that you enter on our Site. Our web server aggregates this information in order to monitor the level of activity on our Site, evaluate its effectiveness, and improve the content of our Site in order to make your visit an easy and enjoyable experience.

We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, or otherwise disclose or use any Aggregate Information, provided that such information does not personally identify you. We do not correlate any Personally Identifiable Information with the Aggregate Information that we collect on our Site. If we do correlate any Aggregate Information to you, it will be protected like any other Personally Identifiable Information under this Privacy Statement.

**Sharing Your Information**

Except as disclosed in this Privacy Statement, we do not sell trade, rent, or otherwise retransmit any Personally Identifiable Information we collect online unless we have your permission. Any Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us will be stored in our databases in the United States.

1\. Affiliates.  With a business powered by OWOW, you'll receive advice and information from your own personal business advisory team – a support network consisting of your sponsoring Affiliate and upline organization. To allow such communication, we may share your contact information with your sponsoring Affiliate and upline organization. They have agreed not to share your information with any non-affiliated third parties, and are obligated to observe the intent of this Privacy Statement. In the ordinary course of supporting your business, information about you and your orders must be shared with your sponsoring Affiliate and immediate upline. You have the opportunity to let us know, however, if you do not want any Personally Identifiable Information shared beyond your immediate upline.

2\. Customers.  To assure the highest level of personal service, we may share Personally Identifiable Information about you (excluding credit card information) with your servicing Affiliatess, who are committed to making sure you're pleased with the products you purchase and that you receive a favorable experience. Your servicing Affilaitess have agreed not to share your information with any non-affiliated third parties, and are obligated to observe the intent of this Privacy Statement. You may elect not to share order details or any Personally Identifiable Information with your servicing Affiliates by editing your preferences online in My Account after completing registration, or contact us as described in the "Contact Us" section, below, and we will assist you. 

3\. General.  We may share Personally Identifiable Information you provide online with other OWOW-related entities and/or trusted business partners with whom we collaborate, as well as those that provide services to our Site. Where we engage non-affiliated third-party agents or contractors, we require them also to observe the intent of this Privacy Statement. 

From time to time, we may be required to provide Personally Identifiable Information in response to court order, subpoena, or government investigation. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. We may release Personally Identifiable Information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves.

Should OWOW or its related entities merge with or be acquired by another business entity, or its respective assets be acquired, you should expect that we would share some or all of your Personally Identifiable Information to companies assuming the role of serving you and other users of our Site.

**Data Network Affiliates, Inc - U.S. Safe Harbor for Privacy**

The U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission have developed a "Safe Harbor" framework of data protection principles. This Safe Harbor is designed to provide U.S. organizations with a means to satisfy the European Union's legal requirement that adequate data protections be afforded to personally identifiable information transferred from the European Union to the United States. The OWOW privacy policy is consistent with the Safe Harbor principles, and OWOW has specifically certified that its transfers of manual and electronic data from the European Union to the United States adhere to the Safe Harbor principles.

OWOW receives private information about customers, employees, and business partners from sources outside of the United States including countries within the European Union. We have self-certified, with third party independent verification, that our privacy practices as consistent with the U.S.- E.U. Safe Harbor principles: notice, choice, onward transfer, access and accuracy, security, and oversight/enforcement. More information about the U.S. Department of Commerce Safe Harbor Program can be found at http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/.

OWOW is committed to resolving any complaint from customers, employees, or business partners in the E.U. concerning the privacy of their personal information. In addition, we have engaged the Better Business Bureau (BBB) to serve as an independent alternative dispute resolution mechanism.

**Your Choices**

Your permission is generally secured first. We will generally not use or share the Personally Identifiable Information collected on our Site in ways unrelated to the purpose for which you provided the information, including those described above, without providing you a choice whether to permit any such unrelated uses. Customer information and purchase details, however, will be shared with the Affiliate until the Customer edits his or her preferences online in Manage My Account or contacts us for assistance as described in the "Contact Us" section.

**Accessing and Correcting Your Information**

We take reasonable measures to ensure that any Personally Identifiable Information we collect on our Site is accurate, current, complete, and reliable for its intended use. If you wish to update or otherwise correct Personally Identifiable Information you have provided to us, you may edit your information online after completing registration, or contact us as described in the "Contact Us" section, below, and we will assist you.

**Protecting Your Information**

We acknowledge your trust and are committed to take reasonable steps to protect Personally Identifiable Information you provide online from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access. We employ physical, electronic, and managerial processes to safeguard and secure your information.

It is your responsibility to safeguard the password you use to access our Site, and to promptly advise OWOW if you ever suspect that your password has been compromised. We strongly encourage you to change your password regularly to prevent unauthorized access. Because your identification number and password are specific to you, you acknowledge sole responsibility for any and all use of our Site conducted with your identification number and password.

**Use of Cookies on This Site**

A "cookie" is a small data file transferred to your computer's hard drive that allows a website to respond to you as an individual, gathering and remembering information about your preferences in order to tailor its operation to your needs, likes, and dislikes. Cookies also enable an Internet retailer like OWOW to keep track of a consumer's electronic "shopping cart" before completing a purchase. Overall, cookies are safe, as they only identify your computer to customize your web experience. Accepting a cookie does not provide us access to your computer or any Personally Identifiable Information about you, other than the information you choose to share. Other servers cannot read them, nor can they be used to deliver a virus.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually adjust yours (Microsoft Internet Explorer, Firefox,or Netscape Navigator) to notify you of cookie placement requests, refuse certain cookies, or decline cookies completely. If you turn off cookies completely, there may be some website features that will not be available to you, and some web pages may not display properly.

To support the personalized features of our Site (such as your country and language codes, electronic shopping cart, and other ordering and browsing functions), we must send a cookie to your computer's hard drive and/or use cookie-based authentication to identify you as a registered Site user. We do not, however, use so-called "surveillance" cookies that track your activity elsewhere on the web.

**Use of Active-X and JAVA Applets on This Site**

Active-X programs and JAVA applets are executable programs that can be transferred to your computer's hard drive to cause your computer to perform functions in connection with your visit to a website. Our Site does not transfer any Active-X programs or Java Applets to your computer's hard drive.

**Links to Other Websites**

Links to third-party websites may be provided solely for your information and convenience, or to provide additional shopping for various other goods and services through our Merchant and Services Partners. If you use these links, you will leave our Site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those websites linked to our Site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit.

We maintain contractual agreements with all of our Merchant and Services Partners, which require them to observe the intent of this Privacy Statement. When you enter a Partner Store from our Site, we provide them only with your identification number for purposes of introducing you. In return, the Partner Store shares with us any purchases you make from their websites in order for us to assign proper credit to you and to your servicing Affiliate.

**Children's Privacy Protection**

We take special care to protect the privacy needs of children and encourage parents to be an active participant in their child's online activities. Our Site does not target and is not intended for children under the age of 16, and we will not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from them. If we discover personal data from a child through our Site, we will eliminate that data.

**Changes to This Statement**

Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Statement will be posted here on our Site and the date of the newest version posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any Personally Identifiable Information at our Site, to see if this Privacy Statement has changed. By using our Site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Statement in effect at the time of use.

Contact Us

If you have any concerns about our use of your information or about this Privacy Statement, please send an email to customer.support@oneowrldonewebsite.com. We will make every reasonable effort to address your concerns and remedy any problems you bring to our attention.

Updated and effective October 10, 2010.

Copyright ©2010 One World One Website, Inc.

265 S Federal Hwy #297  
Deerfield Beach, FL 33441

All rights reserved
